{
    "subject": "Lauren_Holly",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Jim_Carrey",
    "human_readable": "Lauren Holly is married to Jim Carrey.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8887289762496948,
            "question": "Is Lauren Holly married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8836362361907959,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Lauren Holly and Jim Carrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8662857413291931,
            "question": "Who is married to Jim Carrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3817650079727173,
            "question": "What is Jim Carrey known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1782192587852478,
            "question": "Has Lauren Holly been in any popular movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07563638687133789,
            "question": "Are there any other celebrity couples you know about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07257609069347382,
            "question": "Who are some famous actresses?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07049689441919327,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a time when two celebrities got married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03605504333972931,
            "question": "Who are some famous actors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03146000951528549,
            "question": "What are some examples of successful Hollywood marriages?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lauren Holly is married to Jim Carrey.",
            "html": "yago_6974_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some famous actors?",
            "html": "yago_6974_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about a time when two celebrities got married?",
            "html": "yago_6974_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some famous actresses?",
            "html": "yago_6974_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6974_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6974_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6974_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6974_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6974_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6974_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6974_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6974_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6974_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6974_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Lauren Holly's marriage to Jim Carrey, stating that they were married from 1996 to 1997. This supports the triple that Lauren Holly is married to Jim Carrey."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Lauren Holly was married to Jim Carrey from 1996 to 1997 and they divorced. Therefore, the statement that Lauren Holly is currently married to Jim Carrey is incorrect based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}